build-reciprocal-links.com 2013-04-10

# Privacy Policy - build-reciprocal-links.com

The visitors (the "User") of the build-reciprocal-links.com websites are in control of the use of information they provide to build-reciprocal-links.com, or one of its current or future affiliate members ("Affiliate Members"). build-reciprocal-links.com is committed to respecting the privacy rights of Users to the build-reciprocal-links.com website (the "Site"). While visiting the Site, we may ask Users to provide personal information ("Personal Information") for purposes of interacting with the Site. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Please see the Effective Date stated at the conclusion of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and dissemination of information that we collect from Users. To the extent that Users disclose any such information to other parties, through other web sites on the Internet linked to this site or otherwise, THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL NOT APPLY TO SUCH DISCLOSURE. Since build-reciprocal-links.com do not control the privacy policies of third parties (including Affiliate Members), Users are subject to the privacy customs and policies, if any, of that third party, and build-reciprocal-links.com shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of Personal Information by that third party. Therefore, we encourage Users to ask questions before they disclose Personal Information to other parties. 

Information Collected.  
These websites automatically collect and/or tracks various information, including but not limited to (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of web browser used to access the Site; (2) the e-mail addresses of Users that communicate with us via e-mail, or users that posted messages to the MyEvent.com bulletin boards, or users that post messages to build-reciprocal-links.com chat groups; (3) Personal Information specifically provided by the User in online forms, registration forms, surveys, and contests entries, and (4) user-specific information on what pages Users access. 

When registering through the website as on the order form or the free trial form, we provide the option for the user to "opt out" of any non essential communications. These communications include newsletters, new product updates as well as special offers. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at pr@build-reciprocal-links.com. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications through your Control Panel, or you may contact us at build-reciprocal-links.com to opt-out. 

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and/or create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. build-reciprocal-links.com store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at pr@build-reciprocal-links.com or at pr@build-reciprocal-links.com to request that we remove this information from our database. 

build-reciprocal-links.com is the sole owner of the information collected on build-reciprocal-links.com. These websites collect personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

Orders  
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (if required, such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. We may also use this information to send you newsletters or updates on your account. Clients have the right to opt-out of non critical communications such as newsletters or new feature updates. Client's may not opt out of critical emails such as notifications of account status, or notification of account upgrades and/or account cancellations. 

Surveys or Contests  
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), to send participants an email newsletter. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

Cookies.  
A "cookie" is an element of data which is a piece of text, not a program and that a website can send to the User's browser, which may then be stored on a User's computer system. The Site can access the information from a cookie sent to a User's computer system. build-reciprocal-links.com does place cookies on Users' computer systems. build-reciprocal-links.com cannot access other cookies sent by other web sites or the information contained therein. We use cookies to track usage of the Site and further customize User's experience when such is visiting the Site. By tracking usage, build-reciprocal-links.com can best determine what features of the Site best serve each User. When a User revisits the Site, we will recognize such User by the cookie and may tailor her/his visit accordingly. Users may decline the cookie by using the appropriate feature of its web client software, if available, however, some functionality of the Site may not function properly if the User declines the cookie. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use a third-party live chat service called Liveperson that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate such as clickstream data in order to better serve our customers. We also use Google's keyword analytics to track clickstream data. 

Log Files  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information for the security of These websites and their clients. 

Use of Personal Information.   
Information to Users.   
build-reciprocal-links.com reserves the right to use the Personal Information of Users to send them information via email about build-reciprocal-links.com, the Site, our products and services, and other topics or products, from theses websites or others, in which such Users may have indicated interest. If a User prefers not to receive such messages, he/she may send an e-mail message to pr@build-reciprocal-links.com or at pr@build-reciprocal-links.com with the subject "unsubscribe". build-reciprocal-links.com reserves the right to contact Users regarding accounts status and changes to the Terms of Use Agreement, this Privacy Policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to the Site and/or to Users. 

Data Analysis & Other User.   
Personal Information collected by these websites either on a form or passively, will be used by build-reciprocal-links.com for general business purposes, including but not limited to editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users' behavior, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many Users have seen or clicked on their advertisements, and to customize content and layout of the Site. 

Sharing of Personal Information.   
build-reciprocal-links.com will not sell, rent, swap, or otherwise disclose the registration data of Users to any unaffiliated third party. However, we may share Personal Information supplied by the User with Affiliate Members. These Affiliate Members will not use this Personally Identifiable Information other than for the express purpose of providing the service(s) requested. For example, when Users purchaser paid service from build-reciprocal-links.com, we provide user's email address and other personal information to our authorized retailer to process their order and verify fraud related activities. 

2Checkout.com and Paypal are authorized retailer of build-reciprocal-links.com. We recommend you to go through their privacy policy before you purchase the services. 

Service Providers  
We use other third parties tools to provide certain services on our website. When you sign up for free or paid services, we will share your name and email as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

No Liability for Acts of Third Parties.   
Although these websites will use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of Personal Information and/or the registration data, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. build-reciprocal-links.com will have no liability for disclosure of registration data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

Security  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at sales@build-reciprocal-links.com. 

Use of Aggregated Information.  
build-reciprocal-links.com reserves the right to disclose to third parties information about Users usage of the Site and any related services, including information gathered during use of the Site by Users. Any information disclosed will be in aggregate data form (such as overall patterns or demographic reports) that does not describe or identify any individual User. 

Access to Personal Information.  
Upon request via postal mail, or e-mail to pr@build-reciprocal-links.com with the subject "Access to Personal Information", build-reciprocal-links.com will provide Users with a summary of any of their Personal Information retained by these websites. Users may modify, correct, change or update their Personal Information or cause their Personal Information to be removed from the build-reciprocal-links.com database. build-reciprocal-links.com will only send Personal Information records to the e-mail address on file for the User name associated with it. 

Children's Privacy.  
build-reciprocal-links.com does not specifically collect information about children, but is concerned about the safety of children and their use of the Internet. Therefore, we will never knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical. 

Testimonials.  
We post customer testimonials on our Web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name, city and state. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting this personally identifiable information along with the testimonial. 

Updates.  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 10th, 2005. build-reciprocal-links.com reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other build-reciprocal-links.com policy or practice, at any time with reasonable notice to users of the Site. Any changes or updates will be effective upon posting to the Site. Regardless of any changes we make to our Privacy Policy, we will only use your personal information in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy in place at the time you provided your information unless you give us your consent to do otherwise. Your continued use of the Site following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes for future collections. 

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, www.build-reciprocal-links.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.build-reciprocal-links.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.build-reciprocal-links.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.build-reciprocal-links.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....

Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.build-reciprocal-links.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.build-reciprocal-links.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.build-reciprocal-links.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

Governing Law.  
This Privacy Policy and its performance shall be governed by the laws in force in the Ohio, USA. You consent and submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of the Ohio, in all questions and controversies arising out of your use of the Site and this Privacy Policy. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Customer Support at +91-9825215822. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact pr@build-reciprocal-links.com. 

build-reciprocal-links.com

Effective Date: Dec 10th, 2005
